Guide to the Rice University Archives Studies in English Literature 1500-1900 records, 1959-2020 UA 057
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
"Studies in English Literature 1500-1900" records
1959-2020
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University.
UA 057
261 Linear Feet 261 boxes
"Studies in English Literature 1500-1900" is a quarterly journal of historical and critical studies that is based at Rice University. The record group contains correspondence between authors/reviewers and the editors; some original typescripts and galley proofs; correspondence on rejected articles.
Biographical / Historical
"Studies in English Literature 1500-1900" was founded in 1960 by Carroll Camden, former chair of the English Department, Rice University, and was first published in 1961. The journal includes critical essays from leading scholars in specific fields and a review essay on recent studies in that field.
Longtime SEL editor Bob Patten, Rice University's Lynette S. Autrey Professor in Humanities, collaborates with an editorial board composed of internationally recognized experts to review all essays submitted. Diana Hobby fellowships support graduate students who work on all aspects of the journal.
In 1998 distribution duties were taken over by Johns Hopkins University Press who makes the printed version available as well as an electronic version through the press's Project Muse. All editorial duties are still performed by Rice University.
Scope and Contents
"Studies in English Literature 1500-1900" is a quarterly journal of historical and critical studies that is based at Rice University. The record group contains correspondence between authors/reviewers and the editors; some original typescripts and galley proofs; correspondence on rejected articles.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Acquisition Information
Materials have been transferred regularly to the Woodson Research Center since 1980.
Accruals
Additional "SEL" materials are expected to be added to this collection over time.
Index Terms
Subjects
Literature; Authors; English literature -- History and criticism -- Periodicals; Periodicals; Universities and colleges
Document Types
corrrespondence; galleys; typescripts
Subjects (Persons)
Patten, Robert L., 1939-
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University. Department of English.; Rice University.
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1959-1996, 198704
  - Correspondence, notices on the founding of SEL, 1959-1961, 198741 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Office correspondence, 1963-1979, 198740 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Invitations to join editorial board, 1969-1982, 198739 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Copyrights grants, 1964-1984, 198738 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Permissions to reprint SEL articles, 1964-1977, 198737 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Replies to questionnaires and surveys, 1975-1977, 198736 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - List of procedures for editorial assistant, 1975, 198735 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Reports to Bursar's office and business ledgers, 1975-1978, 198734 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Budget, pre-1971/72 - 1977, 198733 (Box 29, Folder -)
  - Budget, 1977-1979, 198732 (Box 30, Folder -)
  - Style and Bills, n.d., 198731 (Box 30, Folder -)
  - Reader lists, 1963-1972., 198730 (Box 30, Folder -)
  - Correspondence with Johnson Reprint Corp., 1963-1979, 198729 (Box 30, Folder -)
  - Royalty reports from Johnson Reprint Corp., 1966-1979, 198728 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Correspondence with University Microfilms, 1967-1980, 198727 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Royalty statements from University Microfilms, 1971-1978, 198726 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Miscellaneous reader's reports and reviews (mainly Bob Patten's), 1971-1983, 198725 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Correspondence with D. Armstrong Co. (printers), 1973-1978, 198724 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Correspondence re. advertising of and in SEL, 1973-1978, 198723 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Personnel files for editorial assistants, 1975-1982, 198722 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Annual report models and memoranda, 1976-1979, 198721 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities re. "editorial intern", 1976-1979, 198720 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Correspondence with Johns Hopkins University Press, 1977-1978, 198719 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Correspondence with Frank Vandiver, 1977-1980, 198718 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - Copy information and correspondence, 1978-1980, 198717 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Patten to editorial staff, 1978-1980, 198716 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Fundraising correspondence, 1978-1981, 198715 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Evans Press - correspondence, 1978-1983, 198714 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Materials re. Journal prices, 1979-1980, 198713 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Subscription campaign correspondence and materials, 1979-1982, 198712 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Summer Intern Proposal, 1979-1980, 198711 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - Correspondence re. advertising of and in SEL, 1984-1986, 198710 (Box 33, Folder -)
  - Evans Press - correspondence, etc., 1984-1985, 198709 (Box 33, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Patten to editorial staff, 1985, 198708 (Box 33, Folder -)
  - D. Armstrong Company - Correspondence, 1986, 198707 (Box 33, Folder -)
  - Copyright grants, 1985-1986, 198706 (Box 33, Folder -)
  - Subscription printouts, 1994-1996, 198705 (Box 154, Folder -)
- Series II: "SEL" Articles, Reviews, Manuscripts and Correspondence, 1960-2003, 198575
  Scope and Contents note
  Original typed drafts of articles included in the correspondence folders within this series.
  - Lists of scholars invited to review articles, 1975-1977, 198703 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Pre-1970 correspondence: 1960-61,1964-66,1969, 198702 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Winter 1970 - Summer 1971, 198701 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Autumn 1971 - Autumn 1973 (Spring 1972 missing), 198700 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Winter 1974 - Summer 1975, 198699 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Autumn 1975 - Winter 1977, 198698 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Spring 1977 - Winter 1978 (including corrected galley proofs), 198697 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Spring 1978 - Summer 1978 (including corrected galley proofs), 198696 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Autumn 1978 - Winter 1979 (including corrected galley proofs), 198695 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Spring 1979 - Autumn 1979, 198694 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Autumn 1979 - Winter 1980 (including corrected galley proofs), 198693 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Spring 1980, 198692 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Summer 1980, 198691 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Autumn 1980 - Winter 1981, 198690 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Spring 1981 - Autumn 1981, 198689 (Box 14, Folder -)
  - Correspondence: Winter 1982 - Summer 1982, 198688 (Box 15, Folder -)
  - Reviewers, 1980-1982, 1986, 198687 (Box 34, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Autumn 1982 - Winter 1983, 198686 (Box 35, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Spring - Autumn 1983, 198685 (Box 36, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Winter-Spring 1984, 198684 (Box 37, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Spring-Summer 1984, 198683 (Box 38, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Summer-Autumn 1984, 198682 (Box 39, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Autumn 1984, 198681 (Box 40, Folder -)
  - Galley - Summer 1984, 198680 (Box 41, Folder -)
  - Galley - Autumn 1984, 198679 (Box 41, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Winter, 1985, 198678 (Box 42, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Spring, 1985, 198677 (Box 43, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs (2) - Winter, 1985, 198676 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs (2) - Spring, 1985, 198675 (Box 45, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Summer, 1985, 198674 (Box 46, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Autumn, 1985, 198673 (Box 47, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs (2) - Summer, 1985, 198672 (Box 48, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs (2) - Autumn, 1985, 198671 (Box 49, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Winter, 1986, 198670 (Box 50, Folder -)
  - Page proofs (4) - Winter, 1986, 198669 (Box 51, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Spring, 1986, 198668 (Box 52, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs - Spring, 1986, 198667 (Box 53, Folder -)
  - Correspondence - Summer, 1986, 198666 (Box 54, Folder -)
  - Page proofs - Summer, 1986, 198665 (Box 54, Folder -)
  - Correspondence, Autumn 1986, 198664 (Box 60, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs, Autumn 1986, 198663 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs, notecards, proof, Autumn 1986, 198662 (Box 62, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs, notecards, proof, Winter 1987, 198661 (Box 63, Folder -)
  - Correspondence and manuscripts; galley proofs, Winter 1987, 198660 (Box 64, Folder -)
  - Correspondence and manuscripts; Spring 1987, 198659 (Box 65, Folder -)
  - Correspondence and manuscripts; Summer 1987, 198658 (Box 66, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs, Summer 1987, 198657 (Box 67, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs, Fall 1987, 198656 (Box 68, Folder -)
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts, Notecards & Miscellaneous - Winter 1988, 198655 (Box 69, Folder -)
  - Galley Proofs - Winter 1988, 198654 (Box 70, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs - Spring 1988, 198653 (Box 71, Folder -)
  - Correspondence, manuscripts, notecards, and miscellaneous - Spring 1988, 198652 (Box 72, Folder -)
  - Correspondence, manuscripts, notecards, and miscellaneous - Summer 1988, 198651 (Box 73, Folder -)
  - Galley proof - Summer 1988, 198650 (Box 74, Folder -)
  - Galley proofs, notecards, correspondence - Fall 1988, 198649 (Box 74, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts - Fall 1988, 198648 (Box 75, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, galley proofs, notecards - Winter 1989, 198647 (Box 76, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards - Spring 1989, 198646 (Box 77, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts - Summer 1989, 198645 (Box 78, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards - Summer 1989, 198644 (Box 79, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards - Autumn 1989, 198643 (Box 80, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards, contracts - Spring 1990, 198642 (Box 81-82, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards, contracts, disks - Winter 1990, 198641 (Box 83-84, Folder -)
  - Contracts, manuscripts, proofs - Summer 1990, 198640 (Box 85, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards - Summer 1990, 198639 (Box 86, Folder -)
  - Contracts, manuscripts, proofs - Autumn 1990, 198638 (Box 87, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, notecards - Autumn 1990, 198637 (Box 88, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, notecards, correspondence, proofs - Winter 1991, 198636 (Box 89, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs - Winter 1991, 198635 (Box 90, Folder -)
  - Contracts, notecards - Spring 1991, 198634 (Box 93, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs - Spring 1991, 198633 (Box 94, Folder -)
  - Notecards, manuscripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1991, 198632 (Box 95, Folder -)
  - Proofs, manuscripts, galleys - Summer 1991, 198631 (Box 96, Folder -)
  - Correspondence, notecards, manuscripts, galleys, proofs - Autumn 1991, 198630 (Box 97, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, galleys, Autumn 1991, 198629 (Box 98-99, Folder -)
  - Notecards, correspondence, contracts, galleys - Winter 1992, 198628 (Box 100, Folder -)
  - Notecards, correspondence, contracts, galleys - Winter 1992, 198627 (Box 101-102, Folder -)
  - Galleys, notecards, manuscripts, typescripts, proofs - Spring 1992, 198626 (Box 103-104, Folder -)
  - Correspondence, notecards, miscellaneous, galleys - Summer 1992, 198625 (Box 105, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1992, 198624 (Box 106, Folder -)
  - Galleys, disks, ads, misc., manuscripts, typescripts, proofs - Autumn 1992, 198623 (Box 107, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1992, 198622 (Box 108, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 1993, 198621 (Box 109-110, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1993, 198620 (Box 111, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1993, 198619 (Box 112-113, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1993, 198618 (Box 114-115, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 1994, 198617 (Box 116-117, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1994, 198616 (Box 118, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1994, 198615 (Box 119-120, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1994, 198614 (Box 121, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 1995, 198613 (Box 122, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1995, 198612 (Box 123, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1995, 198611 (Box 124-125, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1995, 198610 (Box 126-127, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 1996, 198609 (Box 128-129, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1996, 198608 (Box 130-131, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1996, 198607 (Box 132, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1996, 198606 (Box 133-134, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 1997, 198605 (Box 135-136, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1997, 198604 (Box 137-139, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1997, 198603 (Box 140-141, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 1998, 198602 (Box 142, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1998, 198601 (Box 143, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1998, 198600 (Box 144, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Autumn 1998, 198599 (Box 145, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 39 No. 1, 198598 (Box 146, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Spring 1999, 198597 (Box 147, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Summer 1999, 198596 (Box 148, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 39 No. 4, 198595 (Box 149, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Winter 2000, 198594 (Box 150, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 40 No. 1, 198593 (Box 176, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 40 No. 2, 198592 (Box 177, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 40 No. 3, 198591 (Box 178, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 41 No. 1, 198590 (Box 179, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 41 No. 1 and No. 2, 198589 (Box 180, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 41 No. 2 and No. 3, 198588 (Box 181, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 41 No. 3 and No. 4, 198587 (Box 182, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 41 No. 4 and Vol. 42 No. 1, 198586 (Box 183, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 42 No. 1 and No. 2, 198585 (Box 184, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 42 No. 2, 198584 (Box 185, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 42 No. 3, 198583 (Box 190, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 42 No. 4, 198582 (Box 186, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 43 No. 1, 198581 (Box 187, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 43 No. 1 and No. 2, 198580 (Box 188, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 43 No. 2, 198579 (Box 189, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 42 No. 3 and Vol. 43 No. 3, 198578 (Box 191, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 43 No. 3 and No. 4, 198577 (Box 192, Folder -)
  - Manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, galleys - Vol. 43 No. 4, 198576 (Box 193, Folder -)
  - Two essays and peer review (Box 107, Folder unnumbered)
- Series III: Rejected, Withdrawn articles, 1965-1999, 198543
  1977 and 1986 missing.
  - Withdrawn articles - correspondence, 1965-70, 1975, 198574 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Withdrawn articles (A-G) 1969-71, 198573 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Withdrawn articles (H-K)1969-71, 198572 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (S) 1972, 198571 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-C) 1973, 198570 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (D-P) 1973, 198569 (Box 18, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (Q-Z) 1973, 198568 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-R) 1974, 198567 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (S-Z) 1974, 198566 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-K) 1975, 198565 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (L-Z) 1975, 198564 (Box 21, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-J) 1976, 198563 (Box 21, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (K-Z) 1976, 198562 (Box 22, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-E) 1978, 198561 (Box 22, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (F-P) 1978, 198560 (Box 23, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (Q-W) 1978, 198559 (Box 24, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-D) 1979-1981, 198558 (Box 25, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (E-Kel) 1979-1981, 198557 (Box 26, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (Kem-Q) 1979-1981, 198556 (Box 27, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (R-Z) 1979-1981, 198555 (Box 28, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-H) 1982-1983, 198554 (Box 55, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (I-R) 1982-1983, 198553 (Box 56, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (S-Z) 1982-1983, 198552 (Box 57, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (A-M) 1984, 198551 (Box 58, Folder -)
  - Rejected articles (N-Z) 1984, and 1985, 198550 (Box 59, Folder -)
  - Rejected manuscripts 1988, back issues paid and sent to 1987, 198549 (Box 91, Folder -)
  - Rejected essays 1987, 198548 (Box 92, Folder -)
  - Rejections, 1989-1992, 198547 (Box 155, Folder -)
  - Rejections, 1991-1994, revise, 1990-1993, 198546 (Box 156, Folder -)
  - Rejections, 1995, 198545 (Box 152, Folder -)
  - Rejections, 1996-1999, 198544 (Box 194, Folder -)
- Series IV: SEL Articles, Reviews Manuscripts, 2004-2017, 198507
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 44 Issue 1 (WInter 2004), 198542 (Box 195)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 44 Issue 2 (Spring 2005), 198541 (Box 196)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 44 Issue 3 (Summer 2004), 198540 (Box 197)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 44 Issue 4 (Autumn 2004), 198539 (Box 198)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 45 Issue 1 (WInter 2005), 198538 (Box 199)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 45 Issue 2 (Spring 2005), 198537 (Box 200)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 45 Issue 3 (Summer 2005), 198536 (Box 201)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 45 Issue 4 (Autumn 2005), 198535 (Box 202)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 46 Issue 1 (Winter 2006), 198534 (Box 203)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 46 Issue 2 (Spring 2006), 198533 (Box 204)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 46 Issue 3 (Summer 2006), 198532 (Box 205)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 46 Issue 4 (Autumn 2006), 198531 (Box 206)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 47 Issue 1 (Winter 2007), 198530 (Box 207)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 47 Issue 2 (Spring 2007), 198529 (Box 208)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 47 Issue 3 (Summer 2007), 198528 (Box 207)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 47 Issue 4 (Autumn 2007), 198527 (Box 210)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 48 Issue 1 (Winter 2008), 198526 (Box 211)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 48 Issue 2 (Spring 2008), 198525 (Box 212)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 48 Issue 3 (Summer 2008), 198524 (Box 213)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 49 Issue 1 (Winter 2009), 198523 (Box 214)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 49 Issue 2 (Spring 2009), 198522 (Box 215)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 49 Issue 3 (Summer 2009), 198521 (Box 216)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 49 Issue 4 (Autumn 2009), 198520 (Box 217)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 50 Issue 1 (Winter 2010), 198519 (Box 218)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 50 Issue 2 (Spring 2010), 198518 (Box 219)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 50 Issue 3 (Summer 2010), 198517 (Box 220)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 50 Issue 3 (Summer 2010), 198516 (Box 221)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 50 Issue 4 (Autumn 2010), 198515 (Box 222)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 51 Issue 1 (Winter 2011), 198514 (Box 223)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 51 Issue 2 (Spring 2011), 198513 (Box 224)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 51 Issue 3 (Summer 2011), 198512 (Box 225)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 51 Issue 4 (Autumn 2011), 198511 (Box 226)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 52 Issue 2 (Spring 2012), 198510 (Box 227)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 52 Issue 3 (Summer 2012), 198509 (Box 228)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 52 Issue 4 (Autumn 2012), 198508 (Box 229)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 53 Issue 1 (Winter 2013), 210642 (Box 230)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 53 Issue 2 (Spring 2013), 210643 (Box 231)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 53 Issue 3 (Summer 2013), 210644 (Box 232)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 53 Issue 4 (Autumn 2013), 210645 (Box 233)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 54 Issue 1 (Winter 2014) (Box 234)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 54 Issue 2 (Spring 2014) (Box 235)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 54 Issue 3 (Summer 2014) (Box 236)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author folders for Vol. 54 Issue 4 (Autumn 2014) (Box 237)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 55 Issue 1 (Winter 2015) (Box 238)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 55 Issue 2 (Spring 2015) (Box 239)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 55 Issue 3 (Summer 2015) (Box 240)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 55 Issue 4 (Autumn 2015) (Box 241)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 56 Issue 1, Winter 2016 (Box 242)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 56 Issue 2, Spring 2016 (Box 243)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 56 Issue 3, Summer 2016 (Box 244)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 56 Issue 4, Autumn 2016 (Box 245)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 57 Issue 1, Winter 2017 (Box 246)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 57 Issue 2, Spring 2017 (Box 247)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 57 Issue 3, Summer 2017 (Box 248)
  - Original pages, comparisons, author envelopes for Vol. 57 Issue 4, Autumn 2017 (Box 249)
- Series V: SEL Articles, Reviews, Manuscripts, 2018-2020
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 58, Issue 2, Spring 2018 (Box 250)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 58, Issue 1 - Special Issue, Winter 2018 (Box 251)